Guide to the Stanford University, Asian American Activities Center, Records SC0487
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Asian American Activities Center; Asian American Studies; Asian American Theater Project; Asian Staff Forum; Agenda for Action and Take-Over; University Committee on Minority Issues (UCMI); Junipero; and other miscellaneous documents, Accession ARCH_1997_073
  - Asian American Activities Center
    - Establishment and move of Asian American Activities Center (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Asian American community issues: alternative spring break (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Asian American issues: various articles (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Asian American issues: Vietnamese in America (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Asian American New Student Orientation Committee (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Asian American Students' Association newsletter and planning information (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Asian American Studies
    - Asian American Studies: student coalition (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Studies: undergraduate opportunities (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Studies: Soc162 - "Asian American History" (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Asian American Studies: readings (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Studies: miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Studies information (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Studies: faxes from Northwestern (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Studies course development (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Asian American Studies at other universities (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Asian American Studies (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Asian American Studies (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Asian American Studies (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - General Asian American studies (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Asian American Theater Project (AATP)
    - Asian American Theater Project: untitled play (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Asian American Theater Project: "Tree by Water" (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Theater Project: "Goldwatch" (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Asian Staff Forum files
    - Asian Staff Forum newsletters (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Asian Staff Forum miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Asian Staff Forum: event flyers (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Asian Staff Forum: Coalition for Cultural Diversity (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Asian Staff Forum articles (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Asian Staff Forum agendas (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Asian Staff Forum: Affirmative Action Council (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Asian Staff Forum: Affirmative Action Council (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Asian Staff Forum: Affirmative Action Council (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Asian Staff Forum: Affirmative Action Council (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - Bakke Case (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Display: Angel Island (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ethnic theme houses (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - IDP formation (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - KO intercampus network (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Agenda for Action Coalition and Take Over of the President's Office 1989
    - Occupation of the President's office (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Lewis Jackson Case news clippings (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Lewis Jackson Case information (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Lewis Jackson Case flyers, articles, and information (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Agenda for action (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - People's Platform (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Racism: articles and history (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Report on Asian working women (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - SAPAAC News (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Sarling Filipino newsletter (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Daily Magazine (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - SWOPSI (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Teahouse (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Working group on Asian American student affairs (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Yellow English (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Annual Review Panel Report on Stanford's Multiracial, Multicultural Community (Box 6)
  - Asian American Women's Journal (Box 6)
  - Proceedings of the 1990 Vietnamese-American Conference (Box 6)
  - Task Force on Minority Alumni Relations: report and recommendations (Box 6)
  - University Committe on Minority Issues (UCMI)
    - University Committee on Minority Issues: staff subcommittee final report (Box 6)
    - Final Report of the 1990 Annual Review Panel (Box 6)
    - Stanford University Self-Study on Building a Multiracial, Multicultural University Community (Box 6)
    - University Committee on Minority Issues miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - University Committee on Minority Issues (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - University Committee on Minority Issues (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Junipero Asian American Theme Dorm
    This series contains materials pertaining to the Asian American Theater Project (AATP), including copies of early plays. Records and materials pertaining to the Junipero Asian American Theme dorm, redress and reparations for Japanese Americans incarcerated during WW II, and the Agenda for Action Coalition are included. Also included are materials pertaining to the 1987-1990 University Committe on Minority Issues (UCMI).
    - Junipero theme associate information (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Junipero Reisdent Fellow Daniel Okimoto (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Junipero newsletter (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Junipero (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Junipero (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Asian American Activities Center (A3C) records; photos; flyers and programs; History of Asian Amerian Students Association (AASA); Asian American Theater Project (AATP) plays; Asian American Studies; Okada Teahouse; Filipino Student Union; Japanese American Reunion 1993; Asian American Women's Journal; Asian Pacific Student Union (APSU); and other miscellaneous documents, Accession ARCH_2003_212
  - Records, Subseries 1
    Included in this series is a paper written by Judy Wu and Dan Lee detailing the history of the Asian American Students Association (AASA). Also included are Asian American Theater Project (AATP) plays, including a copy of FOB, written by award winning Broadway playwright David Henry Hwang while attending Stanford as an undergraduate student.
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C)
      - Asian American Activities Center letters (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Asian American Activities Center news clippings (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Proposal to establish Asian American Center (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Proposal for Assistant Dean of Asian American Activities Center (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Asian American Activities Center Survey (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Asian American Activities Center mural project (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Asian American graduation reception (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Spring Communciasians newsletter (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Winter Communciasians (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Asian American Activities Center bulletin (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Communicasians (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Asian American Activities Center History Project audio tapes (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Proposal for Intern for Asian American affairs in Office of Student Activities (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Asian American Activities Center Bulletin Guidelines (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Asian American Activities Center Bulletin Funding Proposal (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Proposal for Asian American Cultural Center (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Stanford Asian American Awards (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - OSA Asian American intern (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Asian American Graduation (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Communicasians (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - New Directions in Foreign Policy, South Africa (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Asian Pacific Student Union NorCal conference (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Asian Students Coordinating Committee (SASCC) Newsletter, MIN (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - MIN (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - MIN (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Agenda for Action Takeover of President's office by students of color (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Okada Teahouse (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Eating Clubs (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Photos: Okada, Teahouse, and misc. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - News articles: Asian American Studies (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Asian American history at Stanford (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - The Fortnightly Asian American newsletter (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Activities (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Activities (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous flyers and programs (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Old Stanford publications (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Reflections Korean American Journal (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Asian American Women's Journal (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Asian American Womens Journal (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Asian American Women's Journal (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Asian Pacific Islander Magazine (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Asian American community newsletters (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Korean American Student Conference (KASCON) binder (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Korean American Student Association (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - President Kennedy response to Rainbow Agenda (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - East Coast Asian Student Union (ECASU) Journal (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - East Wind, Harvard Asian American Journal (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Resource Workshop newsletter (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Coalition for Minority Admissions and Financial Aid (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Journals (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Asians and the draft (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - SWOPSI class - Asian American in an Urban Setting (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Statewide Education Rights Network (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Educational Forum Asian Heritage Week (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Off campus events (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Public Service (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - List of Community Organizations in San Francisco Bay Area (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Listen to the Silence conference (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Asian and admissions (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Rescource Center (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - History of Asian American Students' Association 20 years by Judy Wu (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Minority Admission (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Policy changes toward Asian Americans at Stanford (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - I-Hotel flyers (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Asian Students Coordinating Committee (SASCC) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Asian Pacific Student Union (APSU)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union (APSU) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union Conference (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Asian Pacific Student Union NorCal Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Okada Extravaganza (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Asian Americans for Fair Media (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Psych. Problems of Asian or Asian American students at Stanford (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Hawaii Observer (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Asian American Women's Journal contributions (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Against the Grain (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Stanford publications (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - International Examiner Seattle (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - La Onda (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Winds/AAW articles (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous publications re Asian Americans (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Community binder (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Daily articles (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Society of Engineers and Scientists (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Asian American premeds (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Junipero House Asian American theme dorm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Junipero House Asian American theme dorm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Yellow Pearl (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Theater Project (AATP) Plays
      - Play by Bill Yamasaki (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Copy, "And the Soul Shall Dance" (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Copy, "Talking Stories" (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Copy, "Enter the Dragon" (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Copy of "FOB" (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Supreme Court -- Minority Admissions and Berkeley Law School (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - SAPAAC Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Proposition 187 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Kathleen Hiroka, Meyer Cultural Outreach Librarian (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Committee on Multicultural Education (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Shirley Sun Productions (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Disabled Access, Asian American Activities Center (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Admissions report (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Graduate student admissions and findings (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Adopt A Book, Asian American Activities Center (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - SWOPSI Asian American and Model Minority Myth (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Undergraduate Admissions (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Model Minority article (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Asian Staff Forum (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Filipino Student Union Scholarship (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Asian American Arts Conference (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - APS Magazine (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Asian American Demographics (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - AACI Internship (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Asian American work group (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - National Conference on Race and Ethnicity (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Admissions bulletins (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - "The Wartime Evacuation" by Harry Kitano (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Lester Lee denied seat on UC Board of Regents (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Students' Association Binder (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Asian Pacific Islanders for Education and Change at Stanford, struggle of Asian American Studies at Stanford (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Studies
      - Asian American Studies campaign (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Asian American professor search (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Akhil Gupta tenure struggle (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - CSRE Asian American Studies appointment controversy (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Asian American Studies Conference (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Asian American Studies Faculty Seminar (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Asian American Studies/Ethnic Studies (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - "Ethnic Studies and Higher Ed. for Asian Americans," paper by Mike Murase (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Chicano student hunger strike (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Cultural events (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Asian American Students' Association historical files (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Monolid Magazine vol. 1, Issue 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Okada Teahouse binder (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Okada Teahouse binder (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Okada Teahouse receipts (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Communicasians (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Asian Pacific Alumni Club newsletters (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Filipino Student Union Archives (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Asian Pacific Americans in Higher Education (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Korean American Student Conference (KASCON) 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Staff at Stanford statistics (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Green Deans (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Asian American Fraternity (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Reflections, Korean American Magazine (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Stanford Asian Women miscellaneous files and journals (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Asian American Directory (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Alternative Spring Break course reader (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Sourcebook (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Asian American Sourcebook, original articles (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Sourcebook (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Asian American Sourcebook (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Asian American Sourcebook (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Asian American Sourcebook (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Sourcebook (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Asian American Sourcebook, master copy (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Reflections (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Community (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Students Association (AASA)
      - Asian American Students' Association cultural binder (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Asian American New Student Orientation binder (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Asian American Students' Association Issues Chair binder (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Asian American Students' Association binder (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Asian American Students' Association binder (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Asian American Students' Association/Asian Pacific Student Union binder (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Asian American Students' Association Fashion Show and Extravaganza VHS tapes (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Asian American Students' Association, Listen to the Silence conference (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Funding for Asian American Students Association (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Asian American Students' Association (AASA) Education Rights Committee (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Japanese-American Reunion, 1993; Subseries 2
    Records in this subseries pertain to the Japanese American Reunion held at Stanford from September 30-October 1, 1993. The reunion brought back nine of 24 students of Japanese ancestry who were enrolled at Stanford during the winter quarter of 1942. These students, as well as faculty and staff of Japanese ancestry, were forced to relocate to concentration camps despite the protest of then Stanford President Ray Lyman Wilbur. Nine of these students returned to Stanford in 1993 at the invitation of then President Gerhard Casper. They shared their experiences and insights with the Stanford community and were honored at a recognition ceremony.
    - Attendees (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Press coverage (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Schedule and budget (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Fundraising responses (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Research documents (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Research documents (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Trustee letters (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Alumni responses (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Asian Staff Forum (ASF) records; Asian American Activities Center (A3C) records; Reflections Korean American Journal; and other miscellaneous files, Accession ARCH-2010-038
  This series contains photographs, flyers and programs of student organizations, activities, and events.
  - Asian Staff Forum (ASF)
    - Asian Staff Forum Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Asian Staff Forum budget (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Asian Staff Forum memos, email (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Asian Staff Forum memos, email (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Asian Staff Forum memos, email (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Asian Staff Forum memos, email (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Asian Staff Forum memos, email (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - Asian Staff Forum memos, email (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Asian Staff Forum memos, email, flyers (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sariling Filipino Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Reflections Korean American Journal
    - Reflections Vol. II, Issue 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Reflections, submission flyer (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Reflections, production (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
    - Reflections, articles (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Reflections, submissions, browser copies (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Reflections, submissions copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Reflections [publication], submissions master file (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Kappa Alpha Phi (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Asian Americans at Stanford 1977-78, a Source Book [photocopy] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Asian American Sourcebook (various editions) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kulintang Arts classes (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - University Committee on Minority Issues reports (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clippings and articles (photocopies) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Flyers and programs (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Office of Student Activities and other ethnic centers (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Asian American Students' Association: 40 Years of Building Community, 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Asian American Activities Center (A3C)
    - Asian American Activities Center assorted materials (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Activities Center Advisory Board -- bylaws, roster, annual report (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Student Leadership retreat handbooks (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Communicasians (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Records, 1973-2015; Accession ARCH-2016-032
  - Photographs
    - Asian American Students' Association (AASA) Fashion Show, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Theater Project, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Hall of Fame, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Leading Through Education, Activism, and Diversity (LEAD), undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Leading Through Education, Activism, and Diversity (LEAD), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Leading Through Education, Activism, and Diversity (LEAD), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Student Events, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Takeover, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Asian American Interactive Mentoring (AIM), undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Activites Center (A3C) Mural Project, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gene Awakuni Retirement Project, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Taiko, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Korean Student Association (KASA), undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bill Hing Tenure Denial, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Activities Fair, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Yuri Kochiyama, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Asian American Activites Center (A3C) Events, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ski Trip, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - CJ Huang Reception, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C) Staff, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Asian American Students' Association (AASA) Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Inagural Stanford Asian American Awards (SAAA), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Rick Yuen Farewell, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Asian Images: George Takei and Tamelyn Tomita, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Hawaii Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Lane Nishikawa Event, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Sanskriti, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Volunteer Student Organization (VSO) Leaders, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Asian American Graduation, 1993- (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Asian American Centennial Reception, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Asian American Students' Association (AASA) Listen to the Silence Conference, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Okada Extravaganza, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Lunar New Year, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - California Proposition 187 Rally and Protest, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - David Henry Huang Reception, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Jesse Jackson Rally, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Student Events, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Student Events, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Records
    - Asian American Faculty List, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C) News Clippings, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Students' Association (AASA) News Clippings, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Akhil Gupta Legal Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Asian Pacific American Alumni Club (SAPAAC) Directories, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Asian American Theater Project Achievers, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ong Yet Nam, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C) Events, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Hmong Student Union, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Chung-Kuei Chang Articles, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Japanese American Reunion, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Who's Teaching Us Campaign, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 25 Years: Honoring Student Activism and the Legacy of the 1989 Takeover, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Asian American Students Association Listen to the Silence, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)